<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tidbits on Nick64</title>
    <link>https://nick64.me/categories/tidbits/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tidbits on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:05:43 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nick64.me/categories/tidbits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trying Out Fighting Games</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/trying-out-fighting-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/trying-out-fighting-games/</guid>
      <description>When Smash Bros Ultimate preorders went live, I preordered immediately. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even into Smash Bros, I just really wanted to get into it, so I bought it in the hopes of finally fitting in with my friends who all played Smash Bros. And how did that go?
I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched the game in years.
Fast forward to now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to get into it for the longest time. They seem really fun, and the kinda stuff I&amp;rsquo;d be into, but I was really intimidated by all the technical terms players were throwing around and their skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</guid>
      <description>YOU WILL MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!!!
YOU WILL BUY SEVERAL TERABYTES OF STORAGE FOR BACKUPS AND STORING TORRENTED MEDIA OR RIPS!!!!!!
YOU WILL SET UP PROGRAMS LIKE SEARX AND JELLYFIN TO DEBOTNET YOUR LIFE!!!!!!
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY&amp;hellip;.
YOU WILL HAVE FUN DOING IT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
NOW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playstation Stuff and Website Stuff Too, I Guess</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with drama and also just not feeling in the writing mood for a second there (maybe I should write about those things).
It&amp;rsquo;s funny how after the PlayStation 2 post, I played a little bit more on the PS2, but not by much. Also, my GBS-Control died because of how shit of a job I did with the making of it, I plugged it in and it had a lil&amp;rsquo; puff of smoke come out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Widdle Pwecious Home Server</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</guid>
      <description>Today I undervolted the CPU on my home server, so now I can save a little bit more moneyz on power!
That&amp;rsquo;s neat, I guess.
Also plan on upgrading the drives in the future so that I have more space for awesome doodads (pirated movies and TV shows heheheha), and for backup storage too. Not only that, I also want to try to use the server for more things, like setting up Searx or a home VPN for places that I can&amp;rsquo;t use ExpressVPN at (like school or smth idk).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Visitors</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:53:39 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</guid>
      <description>Well, I was hoping this kinda wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen. You know how you can&amp;rsquo;t use personality #27 in front of friend group #5? Well, this website being on my Discord exposed it. Was kinda hoping this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen, but not much I can do now. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this (you know who you are), uh…. Hi. Hope your day&amp;rsquo;s been good.
In other words, here&amp;rsquo;s a cool song that I wanted to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Awesome</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 20:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</guid>
      <description>There are people I would not like to be associated with that are actively making me feel worse and I do not want to be involved with them. Why do I feel this way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo or Jekyll?</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m debating whether I should go through the effort of learning Jekyll and porting my site to that, or sticking with Hugo. I heard from my good friend realjame that Jekyll (the gen he uses for his blog) is better to him after he tried using Hugo because of the convenience of the tools, but it could just be that he&amp;rsquo;s used to it. I&amp;rsquo;ll think on this a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Really Feeling It Today</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 20:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</guid>
      <description>Wanted to write a lot earlier, but honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like it right now, I&amp;rsquo;m just kind of burnt out from working on my art stuff and just doing nothing. Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallo!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</guid>
      <description>HALLO GAIS!!!!!! MY NAME IS KONATA IZUMI DESUUUU I AM WATCHING LUCKY STARRR wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
It&amp;rsquo;s ok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sega Genesis is so sexy...</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</guid>
      <description>Oh man, oh man, I bought a Sega Genesis for 16 dollars today at Goodwill. Opened it up to get a look-see inside and oh my&amp;hellip; old hardware and huge chips are so hot&amp;hellip; I really dig the look of the internals. Something about the humongous 68000 CPU and the SEGA chips and the Zilog CPU, MAN! It is so AWESOME AND HOTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT. Old hardware is my fetish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
