<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts. Maybe I will still shitpost since it&amp;rsquo;s fun but I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Next post might be a review of something. Not sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo or Jekyll?</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m debating whether I should go through the effort of learning Jekyll and porting my site to that, or sticking with Hugo. I heard from my good friend realjame that Jekyll (the gen he uses for his blog) is better to him after he tried using Hugo because of the convenience of the tools, but it could just be that he&amp;rsquo;s used to it. I&amp;rsquo;ll think on this a little more. In the meantime, I should worry about more important things like school, since finals are starting now for me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Really Feeling It Today</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 20:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wanted to write a lot earlier, but honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like it right now, I&amp;rsquo;m just kind of burnt out from working on my art stuff and just doing nothing. Good night.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges. One college sent me a &amp;ldquo;handwritten&amp;rdquo; letter that was just printed for the whole message except for my name on the top. The address was written too, but they spelt my name wrong. How special. It was good though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I also watched Blair Witch Project. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to open my horizons when it comes to movies since I never watched a lot as a kid, but I liked it a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a lot of movies and getting into new stuff recently in order to give myself a broader sense of my own self and the world. Hopefully it helps with coming up with inspritation for projects I want to make, but A) I have major commitment issues when it comes to those, and B) I&amp;rsquo;m getting off-topic here. Blair Witch Project was really good, the style of it was unique and helped set a good atmosphere, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that YouTube horror series and other stuff has conditioned me to fear old 4:3 analog video, so it made it that much more scary hahaha&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, it was a great day. I hope you reading this right now had one too. And if not, things will get better! Hopefully. Kidding, haha. Anyways, good night. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-sleep.png&#34;&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. &lt;strong&gt;This&lt;/strong&gt; is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it. Rain is honestly really beautiful to me, something about the tippity tappity of the rain on the earth and grayness of the clouds and the amplified coziness of my home now that I’m sheltered from the rain feels really nice. Sunlight is fine too, but I don’t find it all that interesting. Maybe it’s just because I’m saying this as someone who goes outside a lot, but only really for school and work and other stuff, I don’t go out for the sake of going out a lot, so I don’t enjoy things like that. But oh well. Anyways, just wanted to write about that because I really enjoy this day of rain. I hope all of you reading this enjoy your days too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallo!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HALLO GAIS!!!!!! MY NAME IS KONATA IZUMI DESUUUU     &lt;br&gt;
I AM WATCHING LUCKY STARRR wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s ok.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/hallo.png&#34;&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RING POP GAMING!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/ring-pop.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well. I wanted to use this website to host said projects, so I should probably get to them now that I have a site to put them on lol. I should also post more art here from my old Twitter sometime. But yeah, have a wonderful day guys, and to those reading, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:34:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is now Decemberrr!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is so awesome guys!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok good nite&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Time Watching Evangelion 3.0 &#43; 1.0: Thrice Upon a Time in IMAX.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was mid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me clarify. I&amp;hellip; like this movie. Not a lot, but I like it. I think watching it in theaters has made me appreciate some aspects of the movie a lot, some of the scenes were really cool to see in theaters (especially the scene of Asuka trying to penetrate Unit 13) and the music was really cool and epic to hear, but the IMAX presentation felt somewhat&amp;hellip; lacking, I guess? It didn&amp;rsquo;t feel as punchy as I had hoped. And all these things also don&amp;rsquo;t help with the story of the movie itself and how things go, which I have quite a few issues with some parts, mainly the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was it a waste of 2 hours and 45 minutes of my life? No, not at all. Would I willingly watch it again? No. At most, I&amp;rsquo;ll buy the Blu-ray once it comes out so I can complete my Evangelion Blu-ray collection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is sad to see that this is the end of Evangelion though&amp;hellip; supposedly. Knowing how much of a cash cow Evangelion is, it inevitably will return somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for now&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/owari.png&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also this is the last post of the month :(&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Twitter... and Email!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a new Twitter, so woohoo&amp;hellip; and hey, I also made a new email! Both are in the &amp;ldquo;Contacts&amp;rdquo; tab if you want to contact me. Just wanted to make that post real quick. I&amp;rsquo;ll write some more later today, I&amp;rsquo;m about to go watch Evangelion 3.0 + 1.0 in IMAX, so yay&amp;hellip; End of Evangelion is still better. I&amp;rsquo;ll talk more on that later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sega Genesis is so sexy...</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh man, oh man, I bought a Sega Genesis for 16 dollars today at Goodwill. Opened it up to get a look-see inside and oh my&amp;hellip; old hardware and huge chips are so hot&amp;hellip; I really dig the look of the internals. Something about the humongous 68000 CPU and the SEGA chips and the Zilog CPU, MAN! It is so AWESOME AND HOTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT. Old hardware is my fetish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/genesis.png&#34;&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know…. I’ll update with a new post when I get my Twitter stuff figured out, but honestly I don’t really care enough to panic about it right now and fix everything, I have better things to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got the Gurren Lagann Blu-Ray box set.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally got the Gurren Lagann box set in my mail today after ordering it on the RightStufAnime Black Friday sale and waiting a week for it to arrive. Being my first Aniplex box set, DAMN was it expensive. But it was worth it, it&amp;rsquo;s really nice. I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished the series yet but I wanted it because it was fire. Will waste more moneyz on future box sets in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/gurrenlagann.png&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the intro video here :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FwgMxjhXkKo&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a Melancholy Christmas...</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite what marketing wants me to think, &lt;strong&gt;after&lt;/strong&gt; Thanksgiving will always be the start of Christmas and the winter season. Except the &amp;ldquo;hype&amp;rdquo; for me is&amp;hellip; strange. I do feel genuinely excited for Christmas because the mood of the holiday is really nice and cozy for me. But at the same time, it also feels somewhat depressing too. Something about Christmas and the winter season, while I like, makes me feel melancholic as well. Winter is my favorite season, period. But somehow it makes me feel alone as well. When I think about Christmas, I think about being with your family and friends, and I have family, but friends&amp;hellip; not really. At least, not in person. I&amp;rsquo;ve been living in Arizona for about 2 and a half years now as a former Washington resident. Since then, while it was really hard for me to get adjusted most of the time being here, in recent times, I have begun to make friends, but I don&amp;rsquo;t feel any sort of deep personal connection for any of them (no offense to you guys if you&amp;rsquo;re somehow reading this). The only people I really feel connected to are all online, either being my old school/church friends or friends I met through Discord. And I don&amp;rsquo;t want to exclude them or discount them by any means since they mean a lot to me, but I do feel the need for in-person relationships more than online. Something about the feeling of having the people you love in-person with you feels really good to me. It&amp;rsquo;s nice. It&amp;rsquo;s comforting. But I don&amp;rsquo;t have that now. And for a lot of people, the things that define what Christmas is to them may not be that, but for me, that&amp;rsquo;s a defining aspect of it. Anyways, sorry for going on a tangent about this. It was an attempt to contextualize and externalize how I feel about Christmas. This probably won&amp;rsquo;t be the last time I discuss my social situation though. To whoever reads this, I hope you have a wonderful winter and a wonderful rest of your day :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-christmas.png&#34;&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Yawning!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 17:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m about to go to work, but this was a thought I had for a bit every once in a while. My boss will sometimes say not to do something, and somehow, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he does it, he sounds serious, but also sounds like he&amp;rsquo;s joking at the same time. The past few times he&amp;rsquo;s done this to me, I was yawning because I work later in the day, and he said &amp;ldquo;No yawning!&amp;rdquo; in that same way I mentioned before. I genuinely can&amp;rsquo;t tell if he seriously means it or not. It sounds like such a silly thing to not allow, but at the same time that feels like something that would be frowned on by the higher ups of where I work at (a retail store, for context). I&amp;rsquo;m about to go into work in half an hour, but I just wanted to write about it because it was sort of confusing and I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what to think of it, haha&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s just a funny thing to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, I created this shitty website. Thus the homepage and the template were completed in their subpar looks. By the twenty-seventh day I had finished the work I had been doing; so on the twenty-seventh day I rested forever and ever from all this work. Then I blessed the twenty-seventh day and made it awesome, because on it I rested from all the work of creating I had done by watching anime and YouTube the whole day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, yeah this is the first post on my blog. I wish it was more monumental, but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;m not even writing this for anyone more than I am writing it for myself. This post is just kickstarting the blog, more or less. I plan on writing here daily, or at least, as daily as I can handle, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how well that commitment goes. But right now, the site isn&amp;rsquo;t even live at the time of posting, so who knows when it&amp;rsquo;ll go online so that others can see posts like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, for anyone who may or may not be reading this, enjoy the website. It&amp;rsquo;s still under construction, but I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do my best to make it really good and fun to browse. I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding more over time and also begin posting other stuff like art and other projects here (hopefully).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you next post :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>