<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:49:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Should You Make a Website?</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/mimas-room.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It depends. That&amp;rsquo;s a really unconclusive answer, sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of how much effort you want to put into it and what you want to use it for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, I did it because I wanted a place to post whatever I wanted to, like stupid rants or art or whatnot. It also gives me an outlet to be more creative about my profile, instead of a place like Twitter where it&amp;rsquo;s simply just the profile picture, background, and profile text, and that&amp;rsquo;s it. It&amp;rsquo;s not bad if you don&amp;rsquo;t mind it, I just really wanted to have somewhere more open and customizable to let my thoughts out on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be clear, I didn&amp;rsquo;t leave Twitter behind and make this site because of the whole Elon killing Twitter thing people were freaking out about it, just wanted to have a website. But while I&amp;rsquo;m at that topic, censorship is another thing too. I never really dealt with the censorship, so I can&amp;rsquo;t comment on the policies on other sites, but if that&amp;rsquo;s something you&amp;rsquo;re worried about, this is good then. I may not have things that need to be censored on here (I think) but it&amp;rsquo;s nice to know that nobody can take me down. Except the government, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the freedom of having your own platform is nice, but it was also really fun to customize the site and a great learning experience as well. I was not good with HTML or CSS prior to this, and I&amp;rsquo;m still not, but I did learn new stuff and, most importantly, I had a lot of fun changing things up every once in a while and writing posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think another nice thing is that despite pretty much nobody at the time of writing checking the site as far as I know, I feel like it&amp;rsquo;s more comfy to have an audience that actually cares about checking into your sites and looking at your posts (or RSS) rather than people on Twitter who just scroll and like posts mindlessly. When you have a website dedicated to your content and not surrounded by other people&amp;rsquo;s content and also exposed to people who don&amp;rsquo;t care about your type of content, I feel like the connection to the audience feels more genuine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, making a website isn&amp;rsquo;t something that&amp;rsquo;s for everyone, but if you want to ensure freedom of speech, want to have more customization, but most importantly, have a lot of fun, this is a cool thing to do. There might be other reasons too, but those are the reasons I thought about myself and I feel like the biggest reasons for other people too. But hey, I&amp;rsquo;m just a random guy on the internet, so it&amp;rsquo;s up to you what you want to listen to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading, and have a good day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;YOU WILL MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU WILL BUY SEVERAL TERABYTES OF STORAGE FOR BACKUPS AND STORING TORRENTED MEDIA OR RIPS!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU WILL SET UP PROGRAMS LIKE SEARX AND JELLYFIN TO DEBOTNET YOUR LIFE!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND MOST IMPORTANTLY&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU WILL HAVE FUN DOING IT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/anime-typing.gif&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Overhaul!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:29:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As you can see now, the website has quite a different look to it. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it as the final one, but I&amp;rsquo;m really digging the look of it. It also took me like a week to make because I&amp;rsquo;m bad at HTML + CSS :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I hope whoever sees this enjoys it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, I have been playing other stuff like Persona 3 now, and also working on my short comic. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing more stuff to distract myself, but in the end, I still feel not very great&amp;hellip; Perhaps I should write about that. Maybe next time I get the motivation to write again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is really late as of publishing, so have a good night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/anime-cat.gif&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playstation Stuff and Website Stuff Too, I Guess</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with drama and also just not feeling in the writing mood for a second there (maybe I should write about those things).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny how after the PlayStation 2 post, I played a little bit more on the PS2, but not by much. Also, my GBS-Control died because of how shit of a job I did with the making of it, I plugged it in and it had a lil&amp;rsquo; puff of smoke come out of it. Oops. I want to play on the PS2 more though, so I brought out a CRT to play on it. It&amp;rsquo;s not an excellent CRT, but it does the job. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna play Persona 3 on it and also probably try to get better at Parappa 2, but I want to play more games on it as well. We&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also wanted to make a post on the PSP, but I can&amp;rsquo;t actually find my charger for it for some reason and it&amp;rsquo;s completely dead. USB charging doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work either, I think I disabled it or something. I will probably work on that soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been working on a small comic. I have a really bad track record of not commiting to my projects, so I won&amp;rsquo;t say anything about it until I release it here on my website. I would say look forward to it, but you might disappoint yourself if you do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been working on the website too as well, I was experiementing around with new looks for it, but I&amp;rsquo;m not very good at writing CSS or HTML, so honestly it might be while before I come up with something that I want to put in while looking stylish and nice. But I do have plans for renovation, and I still want to implement those new ideas I was talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, thanks for reading, and hope to write here again soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking and Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:48:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/futaba-waving.gif&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry for not writing in a while, I’ve been busy with work and finals and also doing anything but working on the website. I will write more and work on the website during my winter break, I promise. Today I walked an hour from school to home instead of just getting driven back home. It was really nice, honestly. Got to stay outside in the cold Arizona winter air and walk around, see some parts of the area I had never really seen before. I should do that more often, I think it would be nice to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I’ve also been super nervous and stressed out because I had to block one of my friends. I basically was just tired of them not talking to me and all that, despite them being actively online. I mean, how does one not have 5 minutes of time to talk to someone in the span of weeks, right? This was going on for months and months, and they didn’t do anything to fix it, so I’m not gonna do anything to keep things going either. There’s much more to it than that, but that’s not really in the scope of this catch-up post. I just wanted to share it because it’s something that’s been nagging at me for a few days now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to write less bloaty content for the website, and I also want to add more things to it. I don’t want to bloat (I say “bloat” a lot, huh?) the website with random garbage, but I want stuff that I think would be fun to include, so I’m just brainstorming stuff right now. If anyone is actually reading this, you can also e-mail me ideas or DM me on Discord or something. But yeah, hopefully new things will come in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, thanks for reading, and I hope you have a good day :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Selves</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 22:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was thinking about things tonight like I always do and something interesting that I thought about is the fact that there are so many layers and factors to take into account when looking at people. A lot of people define others based on factors like looks, external actions, etc. And no, I&amp;rsquo;m not about to go Kanye mode and say Hitler was good or something. I just mean that when we look at people, we can&amp;rsquo;t really know their true character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, you can get a basic idea because the traits that are the most prominent of theirs are probably on display, if that makes sense. But I suppse someone could just cover up said traits with a facade. How would I know someone is a huge golf fan without them telling me if they don&amp;rsquo;t make it obvious through their dialogue or clothing or whatnot?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like it is possible for someone to expose their full self and their true feelings if they really wanted to. But the issue is to make sense of something like that, you&amp;rsquo;d have to consider their ENTIRE life and background in order for every single piece to fall into place, unless you resort to making assumptions, which isn&amp;rsquo;t true to their own true self. There are things people hide about themselves that could probably never be revealed, for better or worse. And the traits that people do hide are always probably bad ones, whether they know for a fact those things are not acceptable by societal standards, or their own standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there ever &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; a way to truly know a person? I feel like the reason I bring this up is because while I never mentioned it or tried to think of it that way, subconsciously, that&amp;rsquo;s what I made this website to do. This website acts as a somewhat personal diary, revealing aspects of myself that are true to me. I reveal my likes, dislikes, day to day activities, my fears and anxieties, and more. But even then, even if I am absolutely truthful about myself, I will never be able to fully reveal my true self to anyone, both because of things I and others would not accept, and because to include all factors of what make me myself and what factors have to be taken into account as for how I feel when I make a specific post would be pretty hard, or impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what I want to say at this point anymore. I had a concept and a thought in mind, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to put it into words. And this thought is not something I just thought of, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure everyone has. I just wanted to talk about it because I thought it was really interesting and I want to try to put my deeper more abstract thoughts into words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was really nice to type out. Have a good night, and sorry for my delusional rant.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the PlayStation 2 Is Awesome</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The irony of me changing my profile picture to an Xbox character right before making a post shilling the PS2 is uncanny. Was just thinking about the PS2 because of how much I prefer it over the Xbox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was a kid (2013-ish or smth), my parents didn&amp;rsquo;t really buy new game consoles like the PS4 or the Xbox One, so when my dad got an old Xbox from someone he was working for, me and my older brother ended up using it a lot because that was all we had. I remember him playing Blinx the Time Sweeper on the Xbox and never being able to beat the final boss, and also messing around with Xbox Music Mixer&amp;hellip; those were the only 2 games my parents had for that thing. The guy gave like 50 other games in the box but my parents donated them all because they were all rated M ;(.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, off-topic. Fast-forward to now, I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t care much for the Xbox at all, besides my attachment to Blinx (the little scrunkly). Not even the GameCube either, really. I ended up growing to become a PlayStation shill, not just PS2, but all PlayStation stuff. I even owned a PS Vita at one point. But now, all I have is a PS2 and a PSP (I&amp;rsquo;ll write a post on that later maybe).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think for me, the first thing that stands out about the PS2 is the design of it. I like the designs of all the consoles of the 6th gen, but the PS2 is probably my favorite one. Something about the skyscraper-esque standing design of it is really cool to me, the ridges on the system, the boxy sharp design, the cool font on the PS2 logo&amp;hellip; it all just screams &amp;ldquo;awesome&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;2000s&amp;rdquo; to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/ps2.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;&lt;p&gt;My PlayStation 2!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing is the games too. I used to care about collecting old game systems a lot more than I do now, and bought the systems and random games for them for the sake of having them, but the only console that really lasted after that phase was the PS2. Why? Its selection of games is really good. I&amp;rsquo;m personally in it for Persona 3 and I&amp;rsquo;m willing to try out some other games I have in my colleciton, like Jak and Daxter, Metal Gear Solid, etc. I find that a lot more niche games are on the PS2 than on other systems like Xbox, or even GameCube and Dreamcast, probably because of how big the console was. My favorite games on the system are more obscure and odd games, like Parappa the Rapper 2 and Katamari Damacy&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t really know if they&amp;rsquo;re &lt;em&gt;super&lt;/em&gt; obscure, but yeah, I still love them nonetheless. There&amp;rsquo;s also a lot of other bigger games that came out on PS2 that people may be more familiar with, like GTA, God of War, and other big franchises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And honestly&amp;hellip; yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s about it. I&amp;rsquo;m mainly in it for the games. But that&amp;rsquo;s all a game console should be for, right? I&amp;rsquo;m not out buying a game console for the fancy features or anything, I&amp;rsquo;m there for the games, and the PS2 delivers on that. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s a less powerful system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s my post for the day. Glad I&amp;rsquo;m writing longer form posts now, since it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;m filling the site with bloat. Good night!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Widdle Pwecious Home Server</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I undervolted the CPU on my home server, so now I can save a little bit more moneyz on power!&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/yippee-happy.gif&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s neat, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also plan on upgrading the drives in the future so that I have more space for awesome doodads (pirated movies and TV shows heheheha), and for backup storage too. Not only that, I also want to try to use the server for more things, like setting up Searx or a home VPN for places that I can&amp;rsquo;t use ExpressVPN at (like school or smth idk). Even if it won&amp;rsquo;t be that useful, it&amp;rsquo;ll be a fun and enlightening experience for me, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s what matters most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good night, guys! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle: Rekindling My Desire to Read</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure somebody already used that pun but still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a couple of days before posting for the first time on this blog, during Black Friday Week, I finally gave into Kindle shilling after wanting to do something about not reading and bought a Kindle Paperwhite 2021 model off of Amazon for 100 dollarinos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a bit, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use it at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I guess it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea to get a Kindle unless I had the intention to read in the first place. One issue I had when getting it was how difficult it is to read just regular chapters of manga on the Kindle. Instead, reading volumes of manga is more convenient since they&amp;rsquo;re all compiled and stuff. After a while though, I finally got other books, mainly Akira and Infinite Jest on there, although I do plan on getting other books on there as well. I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched Infinite Jest too much since its like 1000 pages and it&amp;rsquo;s sort of intimidating (although I&amp;rsquo;ll get to it eventually I promise), but I did start Akira, and the experience is very good. I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading before I go to bed, so the blue light feature really helps a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, don&amp;rsquo;t buy shit you don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;ll need for sure, but I think this ended up going well for me and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I bought the Kindle, because at least now I have more motivation to read unlike before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy a Kindle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must please Jeff Bezos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodnight :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Visitors</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:53:39 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, I was hoping this kinda wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen. You know how you can&amp;rsquo;t use personality #27 in front of friend group #5? Well, this website being on my Discord exposed it. Was kinda hoping this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen, but not much I can do now. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this (you know who you are), uh…. Hi. Hope your day&amp;rsquo;s been good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other words, here&amp;rsquo;s a cool song that I wanted to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BHa5Qs9KK0g&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like it a lot. Maybe I should share more music I like every once in a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confrontation</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/confrontation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 14:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/confrontation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been too good with confronting people for anything, really. I’ve always been kind of a coward. I don’t like speaking out about issues, because I don’t want to cause problems for myself or make other people mad. But even without confronting things, I still feel like I make things worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I think I made someone mad at me. I… don’t like this person. I feel obligated to hang out with them because I don’t want them to be mad at me and we’ve been friends for a while. But I don’t like being with him because while he’s not a perfect person, nobody is, he can be kind of… problematic sometimes. He has lots of drama with other people, and that’s not my problem, but I just don’t agree with him and his ways. Not to mention, it… doesn’t feel like he takes me seriously. If I ever actually want to do something, like show him a song I like, or show him a video, he just pushes me off. I think that’s on me though, since I’ve always been a somewhat chaotic jokester of a person. I guess it’s my facade to make people notice me, or something, and because of that, no one takes me seriously. But today, I didn’t feel like talking to him. I wanted to tell him why. But I didn’t. I said nothing to him. We were sitting at lunch and I gave him the cold shoulder when he came. I said nothing. He said nothing. Before lunch ended, he left, shoving the chair into the table and walking out. I don’t want to make him mad. I don’t want to make anyone mad. But my coldness and inability to speak out also helps nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not even just other people it hurts. It hurts me too. There is a girl that I wanted to talk to. We’ve been friends for a while, had some drama here and there, but we’ve been on good terms for a while now. I want to keep things going. I want to talk to her. But she’s always so busy. I can’t blame her for being busy, but I don’t understand how she doesn’t respond to me for 2 whole weeks. I don’t even care about having a full conversation, I just want to hear from her again, but somehow she can’t give up 5 minutes out of any of her days to talk to me, even though it’s clear that it’s not like she’s busy &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the time. It’s not like she hates me either… I think.  She seems to care about me somewhat. Or at least, she did. My point is I’m doing my best to keep things going and she’s doing… nothing. I wanted to bring this up with her, and I have before. Several times. Last time I did, I was kind of immature about it, I didn’t like the way I brought it up. And when she talked about it, I just… caved in. I gave up and decided to blame it all on myself. It wasn’t her fault that she isn’t on and never talks to me and I’m upset, it’s because I’m selfish and she has SOOOO MUCH TO DO ALLLL THE TIME. IT’S MY FAULT FOR BRINGING IT UP ALL THE TIME, NOT HERS FOR NOT DOING ANYTHING TO KEEP THINGS GOING.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do I keep blaming myself for this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do I cave in whenever there’s the slightest risk of upsetting people?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why can’t I just speak my thoughts with no hesitation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do people have to be so hard to deal with?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m tired of people honestly. I’m tired of friends. Not all of them, of course. But right now, I don’t like how things are for myself. For the people I like. The people I talk to. I’m just sick of having to deal with the frustration of keeping things in. Maybe it’s not my fault for people having problems. But it is my fault for keeping my mouth shut.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Awesome</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 20:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are people I would not like to be associated with that are actively making me feel worse and I do not want to be involved with them. Why do I feel this way&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/awesome-cat.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts. Maybe I will still shitpost since it&amp;rsquo;s fun but I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Next post might be a review of something. Not sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo or Jekyll?</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m debating whether I should go through the effort of learning Jekyll and porting my site to that, or sticking with Hugo. I heard from my good friend realjame that Jekyll (the gen he uses for his blog) is better to him after he tried using Hugo because of the convenience of the tools, but it could just be that he&amp;rsquo;s used to it. I&amp;rsquo;ll think on this a little more. In the meantime, I should worry about more important things like school, since finals are starting now for me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Really Feeling It Today</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 20:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wanted to write a lot earlier, but honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like it right now, I&amp;rsquo;m just kind of burnt out from working on my art stuff and just doing nothing. Good night.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges. One college sent me a &amp;ldquo;handwritten&amp;rdquo; letter that was just printed for the whole message except for my name on the top. The address was written too, but they spelt my name wrong. How special. It was good though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I also watched Blair Witch Project. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to open my horizons when it comes to movies since I never watched a lot as a kid, but I liked it a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a lot of movies and getting into new stuff recently in order to give myself a broader sense of my own self and the world. Hopefully it helps with coming up with inspritation for projects I want to make, but A) I have major commitment issues when it comes to those, and B) I&amp;rsquo;m getting off-topic here. Blair Witch Project was really good, the style of it was unique and helped set a good atmosphere, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that YouTube horror series and other stuff has conditioned me to fear old 4:3 analog video, so it made it that much more scary hahaha&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, it was a great day. I hope you reading this right now had one too. And if not, things will get better! Hopefully. Kidding, haha. Anyways, good night. :)&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-sleep.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. &lt;strong&gt;This&lt;/strong&gt; is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it. Rain is honestly really beautiful to me, something about the tippity tappity of the rain on the earth and grayness of the clouds and the amplified coziness of my home now that I’m sheltered from the rain feels really nice. Sunlight is fine too, but I don’t find it all that interesting. Maybe it’s just because I’m saying this as someone who goes outside a lot, but only really for school and work and other stuff, I don’t go out for the sake of going out a lot, so I don’t enjoy things like that. But oh well. Anyways, just wanted to write about that because I really enjoy this day of rain. I hope all of you reading this enjoy your days too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallo!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HALLO GAIS!!!!!! MY NAME IS KONATA IZUMI DESUUUU     &lt;br&gt;
I AM WATCHING LUCKY STARRR wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s ok.&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/hallo.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RING POP GAMING!!!!&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/ring-pop.jpg&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well. I wanted to use this website to host said projects, so I should probably get to them now that I have a site to put them on lol. I should also post more art here from my old Twitter sometime. But yeah, have a wonderful day guys, and to those reading, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:34:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is now Decemberrr!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is so awesome guys!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok good nite&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Time Watching Evangelion 3.0 &#43; 1.0: Thrice Upon a Time in IMAX.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was mid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me clarify. I&amp;hellip; like this movie. Not a lot, but I like it. I think watching it in theaters has made me appreciate some aspects of the movie a lot, some of the scenes were really cool to see in theaters (especially the scene of Asuka trying to penetrate Unit 13) and the music was really cool and epic to hear, but the IMAX presentation felt somewhat&amp;hellip; lacking, I guess? It didn&amp;rsquo;t feel as punchy as I had hoped. And all these things also don&amp;rsquo;t help with the story of the movie itself and how things go, which I have quite a few issues with some parts, mainly the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was it a waste of 2 hours and 45 minutes of my life? No, not at all. Would I willingly watch it again? No. At most, I&amp;rsquo;ll buy the Blu-ray once it comes out so I can complete my Evangelion Blu-ray collection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is sad to see that this is the end of Evangelion though&amp;hellip; supposedly. Knowing how much of a cash cow Evangelion is, it inevitably will return somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for now&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/owari.png&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Also this is the last post of the month :(&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Twitter... and Email!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a new Twitter, so woohoo&amp;hellip; and hey, I also made a new email! Both are in the &amp;ldquo;Contacts&amp;rdquo; tab if you want to contact me. Just wanted to make that post real quick. I&amp;rsquo;ll write some more later today, I&amp;rsquo;m about to go watch Evangelion 3.0 + 1.0 in IMAX, so yay&amp;hellip; End of Evangelion is still better. I&amp;rsquo;ll talk more on that later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sega Genesis is so sexy...</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh man, oh man, I bought a Sega Genesis for 16 dollars today at Goodwill. Opened it up to get a look-see inside and oh my&amp;hellip; old hardware and huge chips are so hot&amp;hellip; I really dig the look of the internals. Something about the humongous 68000 CPU and the SEGA chips and the Zilog CPU, MAN! It is so AWESOME AND HOTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT. Old hardware is my fetish.&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/genesis.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know…. I’ll update with a new post when I get my Twitter stuff figured out, but honestly I don’t really care enough to panic about it right now and fix everything, I have better things to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got the Gurren Lagann Blu-Ray box set.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally got the Gurren Lagann box set in my mail today after ordering it on the RightStufAnime Black Friday sale and waiting a week for it to arrive. Being my first Aniplex box set, DAMN was it expensive. But it was worth it, it&amp;rsquo;s really nice. I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished the series yet but I wanted it because it was fire. Will waste more moneyz on future box sets in the future.&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/gurrenlagann.png&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the intro video here :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FwgMxjhXkKo&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a Melancholy Christmas...</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite what marketing wants me to think, &lt;strong&gt;after&lt;/strong&gt; Thanksgiving will always be the start of Christmas and the winter season. Except the &amp;ldquo;hype&amp;rdquo; for me is&amp;hellip; strange. I do feel genuinely excited for Christmas because the mood of the holiday is really nice and cozy for me. But at the same time, it also feels somewhat depressing too. Something about Christmas and the winter season, while I like, makes me feel melancholic as well. Winter is my favorite season, period. But somehow it makes me feel alone as well. When I think about Christmas, I think about being with your family and friends, and I have family, but friends&amp;hellip; not really. At least, not in person. I&amp;rsquo;ve been living in Arizona for about 2 and a half years now as a former Washington resident. Since then, while it was really hard for me to get adjusted most of the time being here, in recent times, I have begun to make friends, but I don&amp;rsquo;t feel any sort of deep personal connection for any of them (no offense to you guys if you&amp;rsquo;re somehow reading this). The only people I really feel connected to are all online, either being my old school/church friends or friends I met through Discord. And I don&amp;rsquo;t want to exclude them or discount them by any means since they mean a lot to me, but I do feel the need for in-person relationships more than online. Something about the feeling of having the people you love in-person with you feels really good to me. It&amp;rsquo;s nice. It&amp;rsquo;s comforting. But I don&amp;rsquo;t have that now. And for a lot of people, the things that define what Christmas is to them may not be that, but for me, that&amp;rsquo;s a defining aspect of it. Anyways, sorry for going on a tangent about this. It was an attempt to contextualize and externalize how I feel about Christmas. This probably won&amp;rsquo;t be the last time I discuss my social situation though. To whoever reads this, I hope you have a wonderful winter and a wonderful rest of your day :)&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-christmas.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Yawning!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 17:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m about to go to work, but this was a thought I had for a bit every once in a while. My boss will sometimes say not to do something, and somehow, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he does it, he sounds serious, but also sounds like he&amp;rsquo;s joking at the same time. The past few times he&amp;rsquo;s done this to me, I was yawning because I work later in the day, and he said &amp;ldquo;No yawning!&amp;rdquo; in that same way I mentioned before. I genuinely can&amp;rsquo;t tell if he seriously means it or not. It sounds like such a silly thing to not allow, but at the same time that feels like something that would be frowned on by the higher ups of where I work at (a retail store, for context). I&amp;rsquo;m about to go into work in half an hour, but I just wanted to write about it because it was sort of confusing and I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what to think of it, haha&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s just a funny thing to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, I created this shitty website. Thus the homepage and the template were completed in their subpar looks. By the twenty-seventh day I had finished the work I had been doing; so on the twenty-seventh day I rested forever and ever from all this work. Then I blessed the twenty-seventh day and made it awesome, because on it I rested from all the work of creating I had done by watching anime and YouTube the whole day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, yeah this is the first post on my blog. I wish it was more monumental, but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;m not even writing this for anyone more than I am writing it for myself. This post is just kickstarting the blog, more or less. I plan on writing here daily, or at least, as daily as I can handle, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how well that commitment goes. But right now, the site isn&amp;rsquo;t even live at the time of posting, so who knows when it&amp;rsquo;ll go online so that others can see posts like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, for anyone who may or may not be reading this, enjoy the website. It&amp;rsquo;s still under construction, but I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do my best to make it really good and fun to browse. I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding more over time and also begin posting other stuff like art and other projects here (hopefully).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you next post :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>