<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Nick64</title>
    <link>https://nick64.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 20:20:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nick64.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saint Nick64 Says Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/saint-nick64-says-merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 20:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/saint-nick64-says-merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Well, this is sort of late, but I just wanted to say Merry Christmas to all reading!
I hope you did something fun today, perhaps hang out with your family, or something. I spent some time with my family walking and eating lunch at the table today, which are two things my family as a whole don&amp;rsquo;t do often. I love my family, but I do feel bad about how we sometimes feel really disconnected from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Out Fighting Games</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/trying-out-fighting-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/trying-out-fighting-games/</guid>
      <description>When Smash Bros Ultimate preorders went live, I preordered immediately. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even into Smash Bros, I just really wanted to get into it, so I bought it in the hopes of finally fitting in with my friends who all played Smash Bros. And how did that go?
I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched the game in years.
Fast forward to now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to get into it for the longest time. They seem really fun, and the kinda stuff I&amp;rsquo;d be into, but I was really intimidated by all the technical terms players were throwing around and their skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should You Make a Website?</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</guid>
      <description>It depends. That&amp;rsquo;s a really unconclusive answer, sorry.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of how much effort you want to put into it and what you want to use it for.
For me, I did it because I wanted a place to post whatever I wanted to, like stupid rants or art or whatnot. It also gives me an outlet to be more creative about my profile, instead of a place like Twitter where it&amp;rsquo;s simply just the profile picture, background, and profile text, and that&amp;rsquo;s it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/make-a-homelab/</guid>
      <description>YOU WILL MAKE A HOMELAB NOW!!!!!
YOU WILL BUY SEVERAL TERABYTES OF STORAGE FOR BACKUPS AND STORING TORRENTED MEDIA OR RIPS!!!!!!
YOU WILL SET UP PROGRAMS LIKE SEARX AND JELLYFIN TO DEBOTNET YOUR LIFE!!!!!!
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY&amp;hellip;.
YOU WILL HAVE FUN DOING IT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
NOW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Overhaul!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:29:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</guid>
      <description>As you can see now, the website has quite a different look to it. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it as the final one, but I&amp;rsquo;m really digging the look of it. It also took me like a week to make because I&amp;rsquo;m bad at HTML + CSS :(
Anyways, I hope whoever sees this enjoys it!
In other news, I have been playing other stuff like Persona 3 now, and also working on my short comic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playstation Stuff and Website Stuff Too, I Guess</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with drama and also just not feeling in the writing mood for a second there (maybe I should write about those things).
It&amp;rsquo;s funny how after the PlayStation 2 post, I played a little bit more on the PS2, but not by much. Also, my GBS-Control died because of how shit of a job I did with the making of it, I plugged it in and it had a lil&amp;rsquo; puff of smoke come out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking and Catching Up</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:48:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for not writing in a while, I’ve been busy with work and finals and also doing anything but working on the website. I will write more and work on the website during my winter break, I promise. Today I walked an hour from school to home instead of just getting driven back home. It was really nice, honestly. Got to stay outside in the cold Arizona winter air and walk around, see some parts of the area I had never really seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Selves</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 22:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking about things tonight like I always do and something interesting that I thought about is the fact that there are so many layers and factors to take into account when looking at people. A lot of people define others based on factors like looks, external actions, etc. And no, I&amp;rsquo;m not about to go Kanye mode and say Hitler was good or something. I just mean that when we look at people, we can&amp;rsquo;t really know their true character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the PlayStation 2 Is Awesome</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>The irony of me changing my profile picture to an Xbox character right before making a post shilling the PS2 is uncanny. Was just thinking about the PS2 because of how much I prefer it over the Xbox.
When I was a kid (2013-ish or smth), my parents didn&amp;rsquo;t really buy new game consoles like the PS4 or the Xbox One, so when my dad got an old Xbox from someone he was working for, me and my older brother ended up using it a lot because that was all we had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Widdle Pwecious Home Server</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</guid>
      <description>Today I undervolted the CPU on my home server, so now I can save a little bit more moneyz on power!
That&amp;rsquo;s neat, I guess.
Also plan on upgrading the drives in the future so that I have more space for awesome doodads (pirated movies and TV shows heheheha), and for backup storage too. Not only that, I also want to try to use the server for more things, like setting up Searx or a home VPN for places that I can&amp;rsquo;t use ExpressVPN at (like school or smth idk).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle: Rekindling My Desire to Read</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure somebody already used that pun but still.
About a couple of days before posting for the first time on this blog, during Black Friday Week, I finally gave into Kindle shilling after wanting to do something about not reading and bought a Kindle Paperwhite 2021 model off of Amazon for 100 dollarinos.
For a bit, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use it at all.
Yeah, I guess it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea to get a Kindle unless I had the intention to read in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fake Evangelion Adult Swim Promo</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/art/a-fake-evangelion-adult-swim-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 16:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/art/a-fake-evangelion-adult-swim-ad/</guid>
      <description>Made this promo while listening to the track in the video, thought of this, and made it this morning. Honestly pretty proud of it, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it really fits in with the style of Adult Swim promos. Maybe a little. I don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Visitors</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:53:39 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/unexpected-visitors/</guid>
      <description>Well, I was hoping this kinda wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen. You know how you can&amp;rsquo;t use personality #27 in front of friend group #5? Well, this website being on my Discord exposed it. Was kinda hoping this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen, but not much I can do now. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this (you know who you are), uh…. Hi. Hope your day&amp;rsquo;s been good.
In other words, here&amp;rsquo;s a cool song that I wanted to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confrontation</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/confrontation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 14:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/confrontation/</guid>
      <description>I’ve never been too good with confronting people for anything, really. I’ve always been kind of a coward. I don’t like speaking out about issues, because I don’t want to cause problems for myself or make other people mad. But even without confronting things, I still feel like I make things worse.
Today, I think I made someone mad at me. I… don’t like this person. I feel obligated to hang out with them because I don’t want them to be mad at me and we’ve been friends for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Awesome</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 20:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/feeling-awesome/</guid>
      <description>There are people I would not like to be associated with that are actively making me feel worse and I do not want to be involved with them. Why do I feel this way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Friend</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/art/my-pink-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:56:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/art/my-pink-friend/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, today I was out and about and I found this little guy chilling around in my subconscious, so I put my finger wwaaaaaayyyy inside my nose until I could touch my brain and I picked him right out. Meet my new friend guys!
My new friend He&amp;rsquo;s a little bit shy, so please be nice. He likes playing tic-tac-toe and drinking Dr Pepper!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.
But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo or Jekyll?</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hugo-or-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m debating whether I should go through the effort of learning Jekyll and porting my site to that, or sticking with Hugo. I heard from my good friend realjame that Jekyll (the gen he uses for his blog) is better to him after he tried using Hugo because of the convenience of the tools, but it could just be that he&amp;rsquo;s used to it. I&amp;rsquo;ll think on this a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch (12-04-2022)</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/art/sketch-12-04-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 21:39:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/art/sketch-12-04-2022/</guid>
      <description>Made this sketch today, I think there are obviously some faults because I am in no way an expert at art or anything, but I&#39;m honestly just proud of the progress I&#39;m making. Granted, I did use a reference, but no tracing or anything, so I&#39;m happy. I need to keep doing these so I can properly understand human proportions and draw better. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Really Feeling It Today</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 20:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/not-really-feeling-it-today/</guid>
      <description>Wanted to write a lot earlier, but honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like it right now, I&amp;rsquo;m just kind of burnt out from working on my art stuff and just doing nothing. Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. This is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallo!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/hallo/</guid>
      <description>HALLO GAIS!!!!!! MY NAME IS KONATA IZUMI DESUUUU I AM WATCHING LUCKY STARRR wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
It&amp;rsquo;s ok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>RING POP GAMING!!!!
For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:34:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/december/</guid>
      <description>It is now Decemberrr!!!!!!!!!!!!!
This is so awesome guys!!!!!!
Ok good nite</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Time Watching Evangelion 3.0 &#43; 1.0: Thrice Upon a Time in IMAX.</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</guid>
      <description>It was mid.
Let me clarify. I&amp;hellip; like this movie. Not a lot, but I like it. I think watching it in theaters has made me appreciate some aspects of the movie a lot, some of the scenes were really cool to see in theaters (especially the scene of Asuka trying to penetrate Unit 13) and the music was really cool and epic to hear, but the IMAX presentation felt somewhat&amp;hellip; lacking, I guess?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Twitter... and Email!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/new-twitter-and-email/</guid>
      <description>Got a new Twitter, so woohoo&amp;hellip; and hey, I also made a new email! Both are in the &amp;ldquo;Contacts&amp;rdquo; tab if you want to contact me. Just wanted to make that post real quick. I&amp;rsquo;ll write some more later today, I&amp;rsquo;m about to go watch Evangelion 3.0 + 1.0 in IMAX, so yay&amp;hellip; End of Evangelion is still better. I&amp;rsquo;ll talk more on that later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sega Genesis is so sexy...</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/sega-genesis-sexy/</guid>
      <description>Oh man, oh man, I bought a Sega Genesis for 16 dollars today at Goodwill. Opened it up to get a look-see inside and oh my&amp;hellip; old hardware and huge chips are so hot&amp;hellip; I really dig the look of the internals. Something about the humongous 68000 CPU and the SEGA chips and the Zilog CPU, MAN! It is so AWESOME AND HOTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT. Old hardware is my fetish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(
In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got the Gurren Lagann Blu-Ray box set.</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</guid>
      <description>Finally got the Gurren Lagann box set in my mail today after ordering it on the RightStufAnime Black Friday sale and waiting a week for it to arrive. Being my first Aniplex box set, DAMN was it expensive. But it was worth it, it&amp;rsquo;s really nice. I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished the series yet but I wanted it because it was fire. Will waste more moneyz on future box sets in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a Melancholy Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Despite what marketing wants me to think, after Thanksgiving will always be the start of Christmas and the winter season. Except the &amp;ldquo;hype&amp;rdquo; for me is&amp;hellip; strange. I do feel genuinely excited for Christmas because the mood of the holiday is really nice and cozy for me. But at the same time, it also feels somewhat depressing too. Something about Christmas and the winter season, while I like, makes me feel melancholic as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex Album</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/art/sex-album/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/art/sex-album/</guid>
      <description>(Posted on Twitter on October 16th, 2022) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Yawning!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 17:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m about to go to work, but this was a thought I had for a bit every once in a while. My boss will sometimes say not to do something, and somehow, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he does it, he sounds serious, but also sounds like he&amp;rsquo;s joking at the same time. The past few times he&amp;rsquo;s done this to me, I was yawning because I work later in the day, and he said &amp;ldquo;No yawning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning, I created this shitty website. Thus the homepage and the template were completed in their subpar looks. By the twenty-seventh day I had finished the work I had been doing; so on the twenty-seventh day I rested forever and ever from all this work. Then I blessed the twenty-seventh day and made it awesome, because on it I rested from all the work of creating I had done by watching anime and YouTube the whole day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/random/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/random/</guid>
      <description>RSSHere&#39;s the RSS feed link for all posts!Here&#39;s the RSS feed link for diary posts!CreditsCurrent profile picture: Apparently their Twitter doesn&#39;t exist anymore, and I can&#39;t find them online so thanks @catgirl140 (account no longer on Twitter)Random GIFs: GifCitiesWebsite made with Hugo I want to thank my friends for being there and supporting me, I&#39;m glad to have them in my life and they mean a lot to me and without them, I imagine things would be different (in a bad way).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
