<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:27:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playstation Stuff and Website Stuff Too, I Guess</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/playstation-stuff-and-website-stuff-too-i-guess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with drama and also just not feeling in the writing mood for a second there (maybe I should write about those things).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny how after the PlayStation 2 post, I played a little bit more on the PS2, but not by much. Also, my GBS-Control died because of how shit of a job I did with the making of it, I plugged it in and it had a lil&amp;rsquo; puff of smoke come out of it. Oops. I want to play on the PS2 more though, so I brought out a CRT to play on it. It&amp;rsquo;s not an excellent CRT, but it does the job. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna play Persona 3 on it and also probably try to get better at Parappa 2, but I want to play more games on it as well. We&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also wanted to make a post on the PSP, but I can&amp;rsquo;t actually find my charger for it for some reason and it&amp;rsquo;s completely dead. USB charging doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work either, I think I disabled it or something. I will probably work on that soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been working on a small comic. I have a really bad track record of not commiting to my projects, so I won&amp;rsquo;t say anything about it until I release it here on my website. I would say look forward to it, but you might disappoint yourself if you do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been working on the website too as well, I was experiementing around with new looks for it, but I&amp;rsquo;m not very good at writing CSS or HTML, so honestly it might be while before I come up with something that I want to put in while looking stylish and nice. But I do have plans for renovation, and I still want to implement those new ideas I was talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, thanks for reading, and hope to write here again soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know…. I’ll update with a new post when I get my Twitter stuff figured out, but honestly I don’t really care enough to panic about it right now and fix everything, I have better things to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, I created this shitty website. Thus the homepage and the template were completed in their subpar looks. By the twenty-seventh day I had finished the work I had been doing; so on the twenty-seventh day I rested forever and ever from all this work. Then I blessed the twenty-seventh day and made it awesome, because on it I rested from all the work of creating I had done by watching anime and YouTube the whole day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, yeah this is the first post on my blog. I wish it was more monumental, but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;m not even writing this for anyone more than I am writing it for myself. This post is just kickstarting the blog, more or less. I plan on writing here daily, or at least, as daily as I can handle, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how well that commitment goes. But right now, the site isn&amp;rsquo;t even live at the time of posting, so who knows when it&amp;rsquo;ll go online so that others can see posts like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, for anyone who may or may not be reading this, enjoy the website. It&amp;rsquo;s still under construction, but I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do my best to make it really good and fun to browse. I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding more over time and also begin posting other stuff like art and other projects here (hopefully).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you next post :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>