<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(
In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got the Gurren Lagann Blu-Ray box set.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/gurren-lagann/</guid>
      <description>Finally got the Gurren Lagann box set in my mail today after ordering it on the RightStufAnime Black Friday sale and waiting a week for it to arrive. Being my first Aniplex box set, DAMN was it expensive. But it was worth it, it&amp;rsquo;s really nice. I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished the series yet but I wanted it because it was fire. Will waste more moneyz on future box sets in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/genesis/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning, I created this shitty website. Thus the homepage and the template were completed in their subpar looks. By the twenty-seventh day I had finished the work I had been doing; so on the twenty-seventh day I rested forever and ever from all this work. Then I blessed the twenty-seventh day and made it awesome, because on it I rested from all the work of creating I had done by watching anime and YouTube the whole day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
