<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on Nick64</title>
    <link>https://nick64.me/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:46:43 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nick64.me/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Widdle Pwecious Home Server</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/my-widdle-pwecious-home-server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I undervolted the CPU on my home server, so now I can save a little bit more moneyz on power!&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/yippee-happy.gif&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s neat, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also plan on upgrading the drives in the future so that I have more space for awesome doodads (pirated movies and TV shows heheheha), and for backup storage too. Not only that, I also want to try to use the server for more things, like setting up Searx or a home VPN for places that I can&amp;rsquo;t use ExpressVPN at (like school or smth idk). Even if it won&amp;rsquo;t be that useful, it&amp;rsquo;ll be a fun and enlightening experience for me, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s what matters most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good night, guys! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle: Rekindling My Desire to Read</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure somebody already used that pun but still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a couple of days before posting for the first time on this blog, during Black Friday Week, I finally gave into Kindle shilling after wanting to do something about not reading and bought a Kindle Paperwhite 2021 model off of Amazon for 100 dollarinos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a bit, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use it at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I guess it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea to get a Kindle unless I had the intention to read in the first place. One issue I had when getting it was how difficult it is to read just regular chapters of manga on the Kindle. Instead, reading volumes of manga is more convenient since they&amp;rsquo;re all compiled and stuff. After a while though, I finally got other books, mainly Akira and Infinite Jest on there, although I do plan on getting other books on there as well. I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched Infinite Jest too much since its like 1000 pages and it&amp;rsquo;s sort of intimidating (although I&amp;rsquo;ll get to it eventually I promise), but I did start Akira, and the experience is very good. I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading before I go to bed, so the blue light feature really helps a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, don&amp;rsquo;t buy shit you don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;ll need for sure, but I think this ended up going well for me and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I bought the Kindle, because at least now I have more motivation to read unlike before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy a Kindle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must please Jeff Bezos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodnight :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>