<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rant on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/tags/rant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rant on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>RING POP GAMING!!!!
For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Time Watching Evangelion 3.0 &#43; 1.0: Thrice Upon a Time in IMAX.</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/evangelion-thrice-upon-a-time-imax/</guid>
      <description>It was mid.
Let me clarify. I&amp;hellip; like this movie. Not a lot, but I like it. I think watching it in theaters has made me appreciate some aspects of the movie a lot, some of the scenes were really cool to see in theaters (especially the scene of Asuka trying to penetrate Unit 13) and the music was really cool and epic to hear, but the IMAX presentation felt somewhat&amp;hellip; lacking, I guess?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/twitter/</guid>
      <description>So my old Twitter handle got banned because I was under 13 when I made the account. I set my real birthday on it because I was revamping my profile and uhh yeah. Fuck you, Elon Musk, give me back my account :(
In reality, I’ll just make a new account, with a new handle and everything. Maybe I’ll expand to other sites like Instagram or something so I can spread my site around somehow, I don’t know….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a Melancholy Christmas...</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/have-a-melancholy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Despite what marketing wants me to think, after Thanksgiving will always be the start of Christmas and the winter season. Except the &amp;ldquo;hype&amp;rdquo; for me is&amp;hellip; strange. I do feel genuinely excited for Christmas because the mood of the holiday is really nice and cozy for me. But at the same time, it also feels somewhat depressing too. Something about Christmas and the winter season, while I like, makes me feel melancholic as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Yawning!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 17:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/11/no-yawning/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m about to go to work, but this was a thought I had for a bit every once in a while. My boss will sometimes say not to do something, and somehow, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he does it, he sounds serious, but also sounds like he&amp;rsquo;s joking at the same time. The past few times he&amp;rsquo;s done this to me, I was yawning because I work later in the day, and he said &amp;ldquo;No yawning!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
