<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posts on Nick64</title>
    <link>https://nick64.me/categories/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posts on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:19:17 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nick64.me/categories/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wow OK I Made This Site Much Nicer Overnight</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/wow-ok-i-made-this-site-much-nicer-overnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:19:17 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/wow-ok-i-made-this-site-much-nicer-overnight/</guid>
      <description>Website overhaul again!?!?!? Yeah, I saw the cover art for a song and thought &amp;ldquo;Woah, OK my site needs to look like this&amp;rdquo;, and here we are. I like it. I put a lot of work into it. I hope you like it too, reader :)
It&amp;rsquo;s all yellow now, I added fancy CSS stuff, and I also added a newest posts section on the front page, so yipee!
Ok, good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should You Make a Website?</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/should-you-make-a-website/</guid>
      <description>It depends. That&amp;rsquo;s a really unconclusive answer, sorry.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of how much effort you want to put into it and what you want to use it for.
For me, I did it because I wanted a place to post whatever I wanted to, like stupid rants or art or whatnot. It also gives me an outlet to be more creative about my profile, instead of a place like Twitter where it&amp;rsquo;s simply just the profile picture, background, and profile text, and that&amp;rsquo;s it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Overhaul!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:29:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/website-overhaul/</guid>
      <description>As you can see now, the website has quite a different look to it. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it as the final one, but I&amp;rsquo;m really digging the look of it. It also took me like a week to make because I&amp;rsquo;m bad at HTML + CSS :(
Anyways, I hope whoever sees this enjoys it!
In other news, I have been playing other stuff like Persona 3 now, and also working on my short comic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking and Catching Up</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:48:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/walking-and-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for not writing in a while, I’ve been busy with work and finals and also doing anything but working on the website. I will write more and work on the website during my winter break, I promise. Today I walked an hour from school to home instead of just getting driven back home. It was really nice, honestly. Got to stay outside in the cold Arizona winter air and walk around, see some parts of the area I had never really seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Selves</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 22:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking about things tonight like I always do and something interesting that I thought about is the fact that there are so many layers and factors to take into account when looking at people. A lot of people define others based on factors like looks, external actions, etc. And no, I&amp;rsquo;m not about to go Kanye mode and say Hitler was good or something. I just mean that when we look at people, we can&amp;rsquo;t really know their true character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the PlayStation 2 Is Awesome</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>The irony of me changing my profile picture to an Xbox character right before making a post shilling the PS2 is uncanny. Was just thinking about the PS2 because of how much I prefer it over the Xbox.
When I was a kid (2013-ish or smth), my parents didn&amp;rsquo;t really buy new game consoles like the PS4 or the Xbox One, so when my dad got an old Xbox from someone he was working for, me and my older brother ended up using it a lot because that was all we had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle: Rekindling My Desire to Read</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure somebody already used that pun but still.
About a couple of days before posting for the first time on this blog, during Black Friday Week, I finally gave into Kindle shilling after wanting to do something about not reading and bought a Kindle Paperwhite 2021 model off of Amazon for 100 dollarinos.
For a bit, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use it at all.
Yeah, I guess it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea to get a Kindle unless I had the intention to read in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.
But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. This is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>https://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>RING POP GAMING!!!!
For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
