<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posts on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/categories/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posts on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 22:15:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/categories/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>True Selves</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 22:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/true-selves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was thinking about things tonight like I always do and something interesting that I thought about is the fact that there are so many layers and factors to take into account when looking at people. A lot of people define others based on factors like looks, external actions, etc. And no, I&amp;rsquo;m not about to go Kanye mode and say Hitler was good or something. I just mean that when we look at people, we can&amp;rsquo;t really know their true character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, you can get a basic idea because the traits that are the most prominent of theirs are probably on display, if that makes sense. But I suppse someone could just cover up said traits with a facade. How would I know someone is a huge golf fan without them telling me if they don&amp;rsquo;t make it obvious through their dialogue or clothing or whatnot?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like it is possible for someone to expose their full self and their true feelings if they really wanted to. But the issue is to make sense of something like that, you&amp;rsquo;d have to consider their ENTIRE life and background in order for every single piece to fall into place, unless you resort to making assumptions, which isn&amp;rsquo;t true to their own true self. There are things people hide about themselves that could probably never be revealed, for better or worse. And the traits that people do hide are always probably bad ones, whether they know for a fact those things are not acceptable by societal standards, or their own standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there ever &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; a way to truly know a person? I feel like the reason I bring this up is because while I never mentioned it or tried to think of it that way, subconsciously, that&amp;rsquo;s what I made this website to do. This website acts as a somewhat personal diary, revealing aspects of myself that are true to me. I reveal my likes, dislikes, day to day activities, my fears and anxieties, and more. But even then, even if I am absolutely truthful about myself, I will never be able to fully reveal my true self to anyone, both because of things I and others would not accept, and because to include all factors of what make me myself and what factors have to be taken into account as for how I feel when I make a specific post would be pretty hard, or impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what I want to say at this point anymore. I had a concept and a thought in mind, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to put it into words. And this thought is not something I just thought of, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure everyone has. I just wanted to talk about it because I thought it was really interesting and I want to try to put my deeper more abstract thoughts into words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was really nice to type out. Have a good night, and sorry for my delusional rant.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the PlayStation 2 Is Awesome</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/why-the-playstation-2-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The irony of me changing my profile picture to an Xbox character right before making a post shilling the PS2 is uncanny. Was just thinking about the PS2 because of how much I prefer it over the Xbox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was a kid (2013-ish or smth), my parents didn&amp;rsquo;t really buy new game consoles like the PS4 or the Xbox One, so when my dad got an old Xbox from someone he was working for, me and my older brother ended up using it a lot because that was all we had. I remember him playing Blinx the Time Sweeper on the Xbox and never being able to beat the final boss, and also messing around with Xbox Music Mixer&amp;hellip; those were the only 2 games my parents had for that thing. The guy gave like 50 other games in the box but my parents donated them all because they were all rated M ;(.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, off-topic. Fast-forward to now, I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t care much for the Xbox at all, besides my attachment to Blinx (the little scrunkly). Not even the GameCube either, really. I ended up growing to become a PlayStation shill, not just PS2, but all PlayStation stuff. I even owned a PS Vita at one point. But now, all I have is a PS2 and a PSP (I&amp;rsquo;ll write a post on that later maybe).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think for me, the first thing that stands out about the PS2 is the design of it. I like the designs of all the consoles of the 6th gen, but the PS2 is probably my favorite one. Something about the skyscraper-esque standing design of it is really cool to me, the ridges on the system, the boxy sharp design, the cool font on the PS2 logo&amp;hellip; it all just screams &amp;ldquo;awesome&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;2000s&amp;rdquo; to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
    
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;img style=&#34;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;border:0.25em solid black;&#34; src=&#34;images/ps2.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;&lt;p&gt;My PlayStation 2!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing is the games too. I used to care about collecting old game systems a lot more than I do now, and bought the systems and random games for them for the sake of having them, but the only console that really lasted after that phase was the PS2. Why? Its selection of games is really good. I&amp;rsquo;m personally in it for Persona 3 and I&amp;rsquo;m willing to try out some other games I have in my colleciton, like Jak and Daxter, Metal Gear Solid, etc. I find that a lot more niche games are on the PS2 than on other systems like Xbox, or even GameCube and Dreamcast, probably because of how big the console was. My favorite games on the system are more obscure and odd games, like Parappa the Rapper 2 and Katamari Damacy&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t really know if they&amp;rsquo;re &lt;em&gt;super&lt;/em&gt; obscure, but yeah, I still love them nonetheless. There&amp;rsquo;s also a lot of other bigger games that came out on PS2 that people may be more familiar with, like GTA, God of War, and other big franchises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And honestly&amp;hellip; yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s about it. I&amp;rsquo;m mainly in it for the games. But that&amp;rsquo;s all a game console should be for, right? I&amp;rsquo;m not out buying a game console for the fancy features or anything, I&amp;rsquo;m there for the games, and the PS2 delivers on that. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s a less powerful system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s my post for the day. Glad I&amp;rsquo;m writing longer form posts now, since it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;m filling the site with bloat. Good night!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle: Rekindling My Desire to Read</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/kindle-rekindling-my-desire-to-read/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure somebody already used that pun but still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a couple of days before posting for the first time on this blog, during Black Friday Week, I finally gave into Kindle shilling after wanting to do something about not reading and bought a Kindle Paperwhite 2021 model off of Amazon for 100 dollarinos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a bit, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use it at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I guess it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea to get a Kindle unless I had the intention to read in the first place. One issue I had when getting it was how difficult it is to read just regular chapters of manga on the Kindle. Instead, reading volumes of manga is more convenient since they&amp;rsquo;re all compiled and stuff. After a while though, I finally got other books, mainly Akira and Infinite Jest on there, although I do plan on getting other books on there as well. I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched Infinite Jest too much since its like 1000 pages and it&amp;rsquo;s sort of intimidating (although I&amp;rsquo;ll get to it eventually I promise), but I did start Akira, and the experience is very good. I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading before I go to bed, so the blue light feature really helps a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, don&amp;rsquo;t buy shit you don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;ll need for sure, but I think this ended up going well for me and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I bought the Kindle, because at least now I have more motivation to read unlike before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy a Kindle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must please Jeff Bezos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodnight :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts. Maybe I will still shitpost since it&amp;rsquo;s fun but I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Next post might be a review of something. Not sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges. One college sent me a &amp;ldquo;handwritten&amp;rdquo; letter that was just printed for the whole message except for my name on the top. The address was written too, but they spelt my name wrong. How special. It was good though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I also watched Blair Witch Project. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to open my horizons when it comes to movies since I never watched a lot as a kid, but I liked it a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a lot of movies and getting into new stuff recently in order to give myself a broader sense of my own self and the world. Hopefully it helps with coming up with inspritation for projects I want to make, but A) I have major commitment issues when it comes to those, and B) I&amp;rsquo;m getting off-topic here. Blair Witch Project was really good, the style of it was unique and helped set a good atmosphere, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that YouTube horror series and other stuff has conditioned me to fear old 4:3 analog video, so it made it that much more scary hahaha&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, it was a great day. I hope you reading this right now had one too. And if not, things will get better! Hopefully. Kidding, haha. Anyways, good night. :)&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-sleep.png&#34;&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. &lt;strong&gt;This&lt;/strong&gt; is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it. Rain is honestly really beautiful to me, something about the tippity tappity of the rain on the earth and grayness of the clouds and the amplified coziness of my home now that I’m sheltered from the rain feels really nice. Sunlight is fine too, but I don’t find it all that interesting. Maybe it’s just because I’m saying this as someone who goes outside a lot, but only really for school and work and other stuff, I don’t go out for the sake of going out a lot, so I don’t enjoy things like that. But oh well. Anyways, just wanted to write about that because I really enjoy this day of rain. I hope all of you reading this enjoy your days too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RING POP GAMING!!!!&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/ring-pop.jpg&#34;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well. I wanted to use this website to host said projects, so I should probably get to them now that I have a site to put them on lol. I should also post more art here from my old Twitter sometime. But yeah, have a wonderful day guys, and to those reading, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>