<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posts on Nick64</title>
    <link>http://nick64.me/categories/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posts on Nick64</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2022 Nick64 oh wait i dont care</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nick64.me/categories/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fuck</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/fuck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post yesterday. Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind too much because I think I want to try to actually make good content rather than fulfil a deadline and make shitposts. Anyways, today was a wild day, I saw a hit and run with a guy on a motorcycle and other stuff too, it was kinda chaotic and I think I need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But back to posting, I might start not posting as often so that I have time to craft better posts. Maybe I will still shitpost since it&amp;rsquo;s fun but I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Next post might be a review of something. Not sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/more-rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a really nice day. It actually rained a lot more than I thought, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d only rain for the morning, but it rained the whole day, which was really refreshing and set a good mood for me. I also worked on the website and fixed some RSS stuff, worked on my new project (which I won&amp;rsquo;t say much about right now hehe), and also got more letters from colleges. One college sent me a &amp;ldquo;handwritten&amp;rdquo; letter that was just printed for the whole message except for my name on the top. The address was written too, but they spelt my name wrong. How special. It was good though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I also watched Blair Witch Project. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to open my horizons when it comes to movies since I never watched a lot as a kid, but I liked it a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a lot of movies and getting into new stuff recently in order to give myself a broader sense of my own self and the world. Hopefully it helps with coming up with inspritation for projects I want to make, but A) I have major commitment issues when it comes to those, and B) I&amp;rsquo;m getting off-topic here. Blair Witch Project was really good, the style of it was unique and helped set a good atmosphere, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that YouTube horror series and other stuff has conditioned me to fear old 4:3 analog video, so it made it that much more scary hahaha&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, it was a great day. I hope you reading this right now had one too. And if not, things will get better! Hopefully. Kidding, haha. Anyways, good night. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/shinji-sleep.png&#34;&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:34:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a beautiful rainy day where I’m at right now. No sunlight, all clouds, rain pouring down. &lt;strong&gt;This&lt;/strong&gt; is a nice day for me. I personally don’t like the sun too much. Especially here in Arizona, where it gets so hot and all. When it rains, it’s really refreshing, especially growing up in Washington, where there’s a lot more rain than here. I think a reason I like the rain more is just the atmosphere of it. Rain is honestly really beautiful to me, something about the tippity tappity of the rain on the earth and grayness of the clouds and the amplified coziness of my home now that I’m sheltered from the rain feels really nice. Sunlight is fine too, but I don’t find it all that interesting. Maybe it’s just because I’m saying this as someone who goes outside a lot, but only really for school and work and other stuff, I don’t go out for the sake of going out a lot, so I don’t enjoy things like that. But oh well. Anyways, just wanted to write about that because I really enjoy this day of rain. I hope all of you reading this enjoy your days too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RING POP PROGRAMMING!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>nick@nick64.me (Nick64)</author>
      <guid>http://nick64.me/diary/2022/12/ring-pop-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RING POP GAMING!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style=&#34;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;display:block;max-width:600px;max-height:auto;&#34; src=&#34;images/ring-pop.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For real though, no more weird posts for a sec. Sorry for not saying a lot recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work and&amp;hellip; life, in general. I want to work on the website, and I will still be posting daily here, but fixes and adding new stuff will be kind of slow for a while. I hope to get to it as soon as possible, but at the same time, I also need to work on other projects as well. I wanted to use this website to host said projects, so I should probably get to them now that I have a site to put them on lol. I should also post more art here from my old Twitter sometime. But yeah, have a wonderful day guys, and to those reading, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>